3qdigital.com 2019-12-24

# Privacy Policy | 3Q Digital

## The Purpose of This Policy

Your privacy is important to us, and so is being transparent about why and how we collect information about you, how we use and share it, how we protect it, and your right to have your personal data deleted.

This “Privacy Policy” describes the privacy practices of 3Q Digital Holdings, Inc. and our subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, “3Q,” “we,” “us” or “our”) in connection with the [3qdigital.com](http://3qdigital.com/) website and any other website or mobile application that we own or control and which posts or links to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Service”), and the rights and choices available to individuals with respect to their information.

We use the 3QDigital.com site to describe our company and offer ways to contact us, meet our team, download whitepapers, read digital marketing blogs, and register for events.

#### Acceptance of This Privacy Policy

By using this site, you’re indicating you’ve read and accept our privacy policy. If you don’t agree with this policy, please do not use our site. Continuing to use this site after we post changes to these terms means you accept those changes.

#### Accessing Your Data on Our Systems

You may request a copy of all of your personal data in our databases and systems by emailing privacyshield@3QDigital.com, or sending a written request to us at: 3Q Digital ATTN: Personal Data Access 25 E Washington Street, Suite 420, Chicago, IL 60602, USA. We will respond with a copy of any and all of your personal data on our systems and our partner processors’ systems within 30 days.

#### Removing Your Data From Our Systems

You may request that we delete all of your personal data in our databases and systems by emailing [privacyshield@3QDigital.com](mailto:privacyshield@3QDigital.com), or sending a written request to us at: 3Q Digital ATTN: Right to Be Forgotten 25 E Washington Street, Suite 420, Chicago, IL 60602, USA. We will respond and delete your personal data from our systems and our partner processors’ systems within 30 days.

You may unsubscribe from our marketing communications at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of a 3Q Digital marketing email, by emailing us at [optout@3qdigital.com](mailto:optout@3qdigital.com), or by sending a written request to us at: 3Q Digital ATTN: Unsubscribe/Opt-Out Request 25 E Washington Street, Suite 420, Chicago, IL 60602, USA. If sending a written request, please include the email address that you wish to have unsubscribed.

We collect three different types of data: personal information, non-identifiable basic information and  non-identifiable cookies.

We collect your name, email address, phone number and company when you fill out our Contact Us form or when you request content through our website.

#### Non-identifiable Basic Information

We collect click-stream data, HTTP protocol elements, approximate location, time zone, and search terms. We use this data for research and development, system tracking, helping visitors reach the right page, and to inform future content. This data is non-identifiable. This means we can’t (and have no interest in trying to) use it to identify you or any individual person. We also collect access logs and search strings to improve our site.

#### Non-identifiable Cookie Information

We collect HTTP cookie data. Again, we use this data for research and development, system tracking, helping visitors reach the right page, and to inform future content and to improve our site. Our cookies are non-identifiable, meaning we can’t (and don’t want to) use them to identify you or any individual person.

A cookie is a piece of information sent to a browser by a web server. The browser then returns that information to the web server. This is how some web pages “remember” your previous visits; for example, an e-commerce site might use a cookie to remember which items you’ve placed in your online shopping cart. Cookies can also store user preference information, log-in data, etc. Cookies let sites provide you with tailored information.

For additional information on the types of cookies we use or directions on how to withdraw or change your consent, please see our [Cookie Declaration.](https://3qdigital.com/cookie-declaration)

We do not share your personal data with anyone outside of 3Q Digital.  We will disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.  We analyze non-identifiable information with Google Analytics for internal use only in order to improve the effectiveness of our website.

3Q Digital complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States.  3Q Digital has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, 3Q Digital commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information.  EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact 3Q Digital at:

Email: privacyshield@3QDigital.com  
Phone: +1 (650) 539-4124  
Mail:  3Q Digital, 25 E Washington Street, Suite 420, Chicago, IL 60602, USA

3Q Digital has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMs, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States.  If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please visit the JAMs complaint link at [https://www.jamsadr.com/about/submit-a-case](https://www.jamsadr.com/about/submit-a-case) for more information or to file a complaint.  The services of JAMs are provided at no cost to you.

An individual may initiate binding arbitration, subject to the pre-arbitration requirements of direct request to 3Q Digital and JAMs above, by delivering a “Notice” to the organization.  The Notice shall contain a summary of steps taken to resolve the claim, a description of the alleged violation, and, at the choice of the individual, any supporting documents and materials and/or a discussion of law relating to the alleged claim.

The Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over 3Q Digital’s compliance with the Privacy Shield.

3Q Digital commits to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and comply with the advice given by such authorities with regard to human resources data transferred from the EU in the context of the employment relationship.

The provision regarding liability for the actions of agent processors does not apply because 3Q Digital does not transfer personal information to third parties.

Our sites link to and redirect to third-party websites. We’re not responsible for the privacy practices or the content on those sites.

When you leave our site, it is wise to check the privacy policy of the site you reach. Those sites might place their own cookies, collect data, and use personal information in different ways than we do.

The privacy policy described on this page only applies to our site.

We use data hosting service providers in the United States to host the information we collect, and we use industry best practices to keep your data safe from loss, tampering, misuse, and unauthorized access.

Should we modify our privacy policy, we’ll update this page accordingly. If we make changes to our policy, we’ll treat previously collected data in accordance with our policy in effect when the data were collected.

If you have questions about this policy, please contact us via any of the following methods:

Email: [privacyshield@3QDigital.com](mailto:privacyshield@3QDigital.com)  
Phone: +1 (650) 539-4124%20539-4124)  
Mail:  3Q Digital, 25 E Washington Street, Suite 420, Chicago, IL 60602, USA
